lovedateme.com 2013-09-30

# Lovedateme.com Online Dating Services

**Privacy Policy**

** ** **Information We Collect**

If you join Lovedateme.com as a member, we collect and store all the information you enter, including name, date of birth, telephone number, education, email address, etc.

Non-personal information, such as your browser type, IP address, date and time of your visit we use to derive the statistics. Personal information, i.e. your email address can be used to contact you regarding new services or opportunities in which you can be interested.

We DO NOT share your personal information, including email address, name, zip code, telephone number, etc. with any third party or other members and visitors without your permission. If it is required by law, we will cooperate with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. Lovedateme.com reserves the right to disclose members' personal information to authorities in a situation when we believe that such disclosure is important to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who breaks the law or does an act which causes injury. We reserve the right to disclose any collected information in a situation when someone harms the rights, interests or property of Lovedateme.com, our web site visitors, members or partners.  

Profile information i.e. your user name, your marital status, occupation, education, height, weight, hair color, hobbies and interests, and any other information you enter are displayed on your profile detail page and are visible to other members.

**Control of Your Password**

Your Lovedateme.com User Information and Member Profile are password protected, so visitors of our website, other members or any third parties haven't any ability to access, edit or delete your information. However, we are not able to guarantee 100% protection of your personal information in case of hacker attacks.

Lovedateme.com recommends you to do not share your password with any third party and change your password periodically. If you password has been disclosed to someone else, you should immediately change it.

**Profile Management**

Every member of Lovedateme.com has an ability to edit or delete their information from our database. Once deleted, it can not be restored by us.

A site administrator is eligible to delete profiles if they contain advertising information, any unacceptable content or if a user spreads spam to other members.

**Age Qualification**

Individuals under 18 years of age are not eligible to use our dating services. Lovedateme.com does not register and collect personal information from children who are younger than eighteen.

**More Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please visit Contact Us page and use the form displayed to contact our customer services department.
